Laurel Williams

Greenville, MS 38703 mzwilliams0126@gmail.com +1 662 537 8724

Hello, my name is Laural Williams. I am a 35 year old mom of 2.. I enjoy helping people and I love working in retail.. I have 18 plus years of experience in customer service and I'm always open for a great challenge. Customer service has become my passion and I plan to work in customer until retirement. I am dedicated, honest and hard working. I strive to do my best at all times.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Personal Shopper/Sales Associate

Walmart - Greenville, MS April 2022 to Present

Shop for customer throughout the store Fulfill online orders placed by customers Dispense orders items to customers in a timely manner Greet customers and respond to any inquires about their online orders

CSR - Customer Service Representative

Alorica Calling Center - Greenville, MS October 2006 to Present

Answer incoming calls regarding bill and service

Answer general questions and concerns about accounts and service

Manage customer accounts

Resolves common issue with billing

Booked appointments for clients

Customer Service Representative work from home

AT&T - Greenville, MS September 2021 to October 2022

Answer incoming calls regarding bill and service Answer general questions and concerns Schedule technician appointments

Manage customer accounts Resolves common issue Booked appointments for clients

Shift Manager

McDonald's - Lake Village, AR June 2021 to September 2021

Manage the entire crew Manage and Run Shift

Correctional Officer

Delta Regional Unit - Dermott, AR December 2019 to June 2021

Being a main control officer, I was responsible for controlling calls, entrances and exit within the facility. I was also responsible for making sure family's was able to connect to their incarcerated family members by guiding them on how to get their phones and computers to connect and work. I was responsible for locking and unlocking all the doors within the facility. I controlled all alarms and alerts.

Service Partner

Montgomery Cleaning Service - Oxford, MS November 2018 to January 2020

Basic Cleaning

Cashier Supervisor/Customer Service

Morrison Healthcare - Greenville, MS August 2004 to October 2019

Supervise Cafeteria, input schedule, retail and sales, generate reports, answer phone calls, Microsoft word, Microsoft processing, public relations

Cafeteria Supervisor

Education

Associate Degree in Business

August 2006 to December 2009

High school diploma or GED

Skills

- · Microsoft office
- Powerpoint
- Microsoft word
- Word
- Customer service
- Office experience
- Cerner
- · Office manager
- Upselling

- Sales
- English
- Communication skills
- Data entry

Additional Information

Skills

- Serving Experience
- Customer Service
- Office Experience
- Office Manager Experience
- Microsoft Office
- Microsoft Word
- Cerner
- Powerpoint (10+ years)

Assessments

Supervisory Skills: Directing Others - Highly Proficient

October 2019

Motivating others to achieve objectives and identifying improvements or corrective actions.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_to_profile/

aa45265aaa7fbe7ed8b1c125cc20d374eed53dc074545cb7

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued

development in any professional field.